Mikayla Munn

574-294-3835

mikayla.munn@gmail.com

Elkhart, IN

SUMMARY

An innovative tech mind with 18 months of experience working as a Fullstack computer programmer. Capable of working with a variety of web development fundamentals and MERN stack technologies. A valuable team member who has experience diagnosing problems and developing solutions. A talented leader with unique ideas and a history of assisting others in understanding computer coding.

EDUCATION

Student I August 2012 - March 2016

Manchester University, North Manchester IN

- Major Physical Education and Health
 - Developed lesson plans and implemented them to children ranging in grades K-6.
 - Presented to a group of professionals in the field at a conference using Power Point as an aid for data collected
 - Volunteered to work with special needs students by using visual cues and tactical cues to assist them in behavior development.

EXPERIENCE

Kitchen Supervisor | August 2018 - December 2020

Aramark IN2WORK, Indianapolis IN

- Developed and implemented communication strategy increasing speed and accuracy of food service to a minimum of 400 patrons daily.
 - Establishing open lines of communication between shifts by leaving notes, verbal reminders, and meetings to ensure all were on the same page.
- Standardized activities of up to 20 food service staff at any time to adhere to all clean and safety protocols resulting in 0 infractions in over 2 years.
 - Ensuring everyone remained on task, while having fun by providing incentives, such as a pop, to maintain a healthy work environment.
- Analyze data and trends to inform operational decisions and purchases keeping cost under budget and maintaining consistent supplies for a fluctuating high volume kitchen.
 - Analyzing how many residents showed up for what meals and

discerning the food order on an algorithm of weather, amount showed up last time, and service time.

Full stack MERN development | December 2020 - April 2022

The Last Mile, San Francisco CA
18-month intensive program covering web
development fundamentals and
MERN stack technologies.

- Executed 3 CRUD capable applications, using source control, surpassing all requirements ahead of schedule.
 - As a thesis project, I used CRUD to create a user, trainer, and admin database.
 - Soda-Diner App, Database consisted of two schemas. 1)Soda 2) Diner. This application allowed users to select a diner of choice and a soda of choice. After the soda and diner were both selected both schemas in the database were populated.
 - Created a blogging website that allowed users to log in with their own credentials. As an enhanced feature, when the user logged in, the users username displayed at the top-right corner of the landing page.
- Supervised two collaborative projects that enhanced the understanding and application of concepts for a group of four students.
 - To explain ideas, I white boarded existing code while discussing possible solutions to solve a current issue. Additionally, I used this method to predetermine potential issues.
 - I helped coordinate the delegations of tasks by discovering each team members strength to place them on the best fitting task. After each team member completed their task, if a team member was unable to complete the task correctly, I was able to assist in debugging and discerning any errors.
- Converted a MongoDB project to a MySql project. In doing so, I defended my reasoning during a class presentation.
 - In my Thesis Project, creating tables that were easy and functional for the admin to use. Implemented a delete button or an update button that the admin could use and could be displayed in a pretty table.

SOFT SKILLS

Communication
Teamwork
Adaptability
Problem Solving
Time Management
Flexibility
Patience
Public Speaking
Social Media

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
Bootstrap
MongoDB
Express
React
GitLab
Node
MySQL
Microsoft Word
Microsoft PowerPoint
Microsoft Excel